×

1 Choose EITC/EITCA Certificates

2 Learn and take online exams

3 Get your IT skills certified

Confirm your IT skills and competencies under the European IT Certification framework from anywhere in the world fully online.

#### EITCA Academy

Digital skills attestation standard by the European IT Certification Institute aiming to support Digital Society development

### LOG IN TO YOUR ACCOUNT BY EITHER YOUR USERNAME OR EMAIL ADDRESS

 USERNAME

 PASSWORD

 Remember Me   

### FORGOT YOUR DETAILS?

 USERNAME OR EMAIL

### CREATE AN ACCOUNT

 USERNAME

 EMAIL

 PASSWORD

 CONFIRM PASSWORD

EUROPEAN INFORMATION TECHNOLOGIES CERTIFICATION ACADEMY - ATTESTING YOUR PROFESSIONAL DIGITAL SKILLS

### [](https://eitca.org/)

The European Information Technologies Certification Institute - EITCI ASBL

**Certification Authority  
  
EITCI Institute**  
Brussels, European Union  
  
Governing European IT Certification (EITC) standard in support of the IT professionalism and Digital Society

    Your current order is empty.

[**EITCI**INSTITUTE  
CERTIFIED](https://eitci.org/ "EITCI Institute")

Privacy Policy
==============

EITCA Academy Privacy Policy
----------------------------

Your personal data will be used to process your order and your EITC/EITCA Certification as in details described in accordance to the European General Data Protection Regulation, i.e. Regulation (EU) 2016/679 and corresponding legal acts of the European Parliament and of the Council on the protection of individuals in view of processing of their personal private data. EITCA Academy operated by EITCI Institute aims to disseminate IT professional competencies under the official EITC/EITCA Certification standards governed by the EITCI Institute for increasing growth of the international Single Digital Market adoption and supporting growth of the Inclusive Digital Society. This is the mission of the EITCI Institute undertaken within the EITCA Academy Programme which constitutes an important mean to implement EITCI Institute’s mission. Doing so EITCI Institute remains committed to transparency on collected personal data, how it is used and with whom it is shared. This Privacy Policy applies when you use our Services as described below.

Introduction
------------

The European Information Technologies Certification (EITC) and the European Information Technologies Certification Academy (EITCA) Programmes constitute vendor independent quality standards developed for attestment of the digital skills and professional IT competencies developed and disseminated to support growth of the Inclusive Digital Society. The standards are accessible from Brussels fully online under governance of the European Information Technologies Certification Institute EITCI, the Certification Authority / Certifying Body. The goal of the EITCA Academy is to provide international framework for professional IT competencies formal evaluation and confirmation with adherence to quality standards and overcoming access barriers. EITCA Academy participation is not limited to the European Union, on the contrary, it offers opportunity to individuals abroad the EU to develop and confirm remotely their strategic IT competencies with a professional certification from the European Union, under the EITCI Institute governed standard. Thus EITCA Academy is characterized by a new approach, alternative and complementary to the classical professional education and training, as it enables anyone in the world to study under the EITC / EITCA programmes and then obtain formally EITCI accredited Certifications in professional Information Technologies issued in Brussels, EU within a fully online conduct, on the same terms globally and without need to travel and study in Brussels physically, thus significantly limiting associated costs and overcoming many access barriers.

EITCA Academy Privacy Policy applies to any Participant or Visitor to our Services. Our registered users (“Members”) share their professional identities in due of Certification procedure and are able to engage with their network, exchange knowledge and professional insights, post and view relevant content, learn and find business and career opportunities within EITCA Academy. Content and data on some of our Services is viewable to non-members (“Visitors”). We use the term “Designated Countries” to refer to countries in the European Union (EU), European Economic Area (EEA), and Switzerland.

#### Services

This Privacy Policy, including our Cookie Policy applies to your use of our Services.

This Privacy Policy applies to European IT Certification (including individual EITC programmes and the EITCA Academy) and associated web and mobile applications along with associated communications and services, jointly referred to as “Services”, including off-site Services, such as our dedicated certification services.

#### Data Controllers and Contracting Parties

The EITCI Institute (European Information Technologies Certification Institute) will be the controller of your personal data provided to, or collected by or for, or processed in connection with our Services most importantly the EITC/EITCA Certification; you are entering into the User Agreement with EITCI Institute. As a Visitor or Participant of our Services (mainly including Certification Services we provide), the collection, use and sharing of your personal data is subject to this Privacy Policy (which includes our Cookie Policy and other documents referenced in this Privacy Policy) and updates.

#### Change

All changes to the Privacy Policy apply to your continous use of our Services.

EITCI Institute (“we” or “us”) can modify this Privacy Policy, and if we make material changes to it, we will provide notice through our Services, or by other means, to provide you the opportunity to review the changes and decide if you want to continue using our Services. If you object to any changes, you may close your account and your certification can be revoked.  
You acknowledge that your continued use of our Services after we publish or send a notice about our changes to this Privacy Policy means that the collection, use and sharing of your personal data is subject to the updated Privacy Policy.

1\. Data We Collect
-------------------

#### 1.1 Data You Provide To Us

You provide data to create an account with us.

#### Registration

To create an account you need to provide data including your name, email address and/or mobile number, and a password. If you register for a Certification Service, you will need to provide payment (e.g., credit card) and billing information.  
You create your EITCA Academy profile by providing your personal data that need to be processed for provision of our Services.

#### Profile

You have choices about the information on your profile. You don’t have to provide additional and non-obgligatory information on your profile, however, detailed profile information helps you to get more from our Services. It’s your choice whether to include sensitive information on your profile and to make that sensitive information public.

You agree that personal data you provide in your Profile will be a part of your certification validation information, that will be publicly accessible via validation procedure of your issued Certification. Your full name will also be printed on the digital certificates itself. Please do not add non-required personal data to your profile that you would not want to be publicly available.

You may choose to give other data to us, such as by syncing your address book or calendar.

#### Posting and Uploading

We collect personal data from you when you provide, post or upload it to our Services, such as when you fill out a form, respond to a survey, or submit information or take a certification examination.

If you opt to import your address book, we receive your contacts (including contact information your service provider(s) or app automatically added to your address book when you communicated with addresses or numbers not already in your list).  
If you sync your contacts or calendars with our Services, we will collect your address book and calendar meeting information to keep growing your network by suggesting connections for you and others, and by providing information about them, e.g. times, places, attendees and contacts.  
You don’t have to post or upload non-obligatory personal data, though if you don’t, it may limit the scope of the Services we are able to provide.

#### 1.2 Data From Others

Others may post or provide your personal data, especially in case their enrol to participate and use our Services (for example in delegating enrolment into our certification programmes by your company colleagues).

#### Content and News

You and others may post content that includes information about you (as part of articles, posts, comments, videos) on our Services. Unless you opt-out, we collect public information about you, such as professional-related news and accomplishments (e.g., patents granted, professional recognition, conference speakers, projects, etc.) and make it available as part of our Services (e.g. suggestions for your profile, or notifications of mentions in the news).  
Others may sync their contacts or calendar with our Services.

#### Contact and Calendar Information

We receive personal data (including contact information) about you when others import or sync their contacts or calendar with our Services, associate their contacts with Participant profiles, or send messages using our Services (including invites or connection requests). If you or others opt-in to sync email accounts with our Services, we will also collect “email header” information that we can associate with Participant profiles.

Customers and partners may provide data to us.

#### Partners

We receive personal data about you when you use the services of our customers and partners, such as employers, prospective employers and applicant tracking systems providing us job application data.

#### Related Companies and Other Services

We receive data about you when you use some of the other services provided by us or our affiliates. For example, you may choose to send information about your contacts to us for improved professional networking activities.

#### 1.3 Service Use

We log your visits and use of our Services, including via mobile apps.

We log usage data when you visit or otherwise use our Services, including our sites, app and platform technology (e.g., our off-site plugins), such as when you view or click on content or ads (on or off our sites and apps), perform a search, install or update one of our mobile apps, share articles or send inquiries.

We log your activities in progress through the certification programmes, as well as your progress through the examinations (and individual approaches).

You agree that each examination approach that you undertake as part of the certification process is securely stored in a tamper-proof way in the examination blockchain, with that property that previous nodes (examination approaches) condition coherence of subsequent nodes. You acknowledge that we cannot remove the history of your examination approaches.

We use log-ins, cookies, device information and internet protocol (“IP”) addresses to identify you and log your use.

#### 1.4 Cookies, Web Beacons and Other Similar Technologies

We collect data through cookies and similar technologies.

We use cookies and similar technologies (e.g., web beacons, pixels, ad tags and device identifiers) to recognize you and/or your device(s) on, off and across different Services and devices. We also allow some others to use cookies as described in our Cookie Policy. You can control cookies through your browser settings and other tools. You can also opt-out from our use of cookies and similar technologies that track your behavior on the sites of others for third party advertising by changing adequate settings in your web browser accordingly with the documentation of the used web browser.

#### 1.5 Your Device and Location

We receive data from your devices and networks, including location data.

When you visit or leave our Services (including our plugins or cookies or similar technology on the sites of others), we receive the URL of both the site you came from and the one you go to next. We also get information about your IP address, proxy server, operating system, web browser and add-ons, device identifier and features, and/or ISP or your mobile carrier. If you use our Services from a mobile device, that device will send us data about your location based on your phone settings. We will ask you to opt-in before we use GPS or other tools to identify your precise location.

#### 1.6 Messages

If you communicate through our Services, we learn about that.

We collect information about you when you send, receive, or engage with messages in connection with our Services.

#### 1.7 Organization Provided Information

When your employer or school or any other third party enrols you for use of our Services, they give us data about you.

Others buying our Services for your use, such as your employer or your school, provide us with personal data about you and your eligibility to use the Services that they purchase for use by their workers, students or alumni. For example, we will get your personal information in case of delegated enrolment into certification programmes.

#### 1.8 Sites and Services of Others

We get data when you visit sites that include our plugins, ads or cookies or log-in to others’ services with your account.

We receive information about your visits and interaction with services provided by others when you log-in with our platform or visit others’ services that include our plugins, ads, cookies or similar technologies.

#### 1.9 Other

We are improving our Services, which means we get new data and create new ways to use data.

Our Services are dynamic, and we often introduce new features, which may require the collection of new information. If we collect materially different personal data or materially change how we use your data, we will notify you and may also modify this Privacy Policy.

2\. How We Use Your Data
------------------------

We use your data to provide, support, personalize and develop our Services.

How we use your personal data will depend on which Services you use, how you use those Services and the choices you make in your settings. We use the data that we have about you to provide and personalize, including with the help of automated systems and inferences we make, our Services (including certification programmes and releated services) so that they can be more relevant and useful to you and others.

#### 2.1 Services

Our Services focus on certification of your skills, but also include how you connect with others, find and be found for work and business opportunities, stay informed, get training and be more productive.

We use your data to authorize access to our Services.

#### Stay Connected

Our Services allow you to proof your qualifications to others by use of certificates we issue and their validation services.

Our Services also allow you to connect with other professionals, partners, clients, and other professional contacts. To do so, you will “connect” with the professionals who you choose, and who also wish to “connect” with you.

In case of related networking services, subject to your settings, when you connect with other contacts, you will be able to search each others’ connections in order to exchange professional opportunities. We will use data about you (such as your profile, profiles you have viewed or data provided through address book uploads or partner integrations) to help others find your profile, suggest connections for you and others (e.g. Members who share your contacts or job experiences) and enable you to invite others to become a Participant and connect with you. You can also opt-in to allow us to use your precise location or proximity to others for certain tasks (e.g. to suggest other nearby Members for you to connect with, calculate the commute to a new job, or notify your connections that you are at a professional event).

It is your choice whether to invite someone to our Services, send a connection request, or allow another Participant to become your connection. When you invite someone to connect with you, your invitation will include your name, photo, network and contact information. We will send invitation reminders to the person you invited. You can choose whether or not to share your own list of connections with your connections.

Visitors have choices about how we use their data.

#### Stay Informed

Our Services allow you to stay informed about news, events and ideas regarding professional topics you care about, and from professionals you respect. Our Services also allow you to improve your professional skills, or learn new ones. We use the data we have about you (e.g., data you provide, data we collect from your engagement with our Services and inferences we make from the data we have about you), to recommend relevant content and conversations on our Services, suggest skills you may have to add to your profile and skills that you might need to pursue your next opportunity. So, if you let us know that you are interested in a new skill (e.g., by watching a learning video), we will use this information to personalize content in your feed, suggest that you follow certain members on our site, or watch related learning content to help you towards that new skill. We use your content, activity and other data, including your name and picture, to provide notices to your network and others. For example, subject to your settings, we may notify others that you have updated your profile, posted a blog, took a social action, made new connections or were mentioned in the news.

#### Career

Our Services allow you to explore careers, evaluate educational opportunities, and seek out, and be found for, career opportunities. Your profile can be found by those looking to hire (for a job or a specific task) or be hired by you. We will use your data to recommend jobs or mentees, show you and others who work at a company, in an industry, function or location or have certain skills and connections. You can signal that you are interested in changing jobs and share information with job recruiters. We will use your data to recommend jobs to you and you to recruiters. We may use automated systems to profile and provide recommendations to help make our Services more relevant to our Members, Visitors and customers. Keeping your profile accurate and up-to-date may help you better connect to others and to opportunities through our Services.

#### Productivity

Our Services allow you to collaborate with colleagues, search for potential clients, customers, partners and others to do business with. Our Services allow you to communicate with other Members and schedule and prepare meetings with them. If your settings allow, we scan messages to provide “bots” or similar tools that facilitate tasks such as scheduling meetings, drafting responses, summarizing messages or recommending next steps.

#### 2.2 Pro Services

Our Pro Services allow paying users to improve their reach searching for and contacting Members through our Services, such as searching for and contacting job candidates, sales leads and co-workers, manage talent and promote content through social media.

We sell Pro Services that provide our customers and subscribers customized-search posts and pages promoting functionality and tools as part of our talent, marketing and sales solutions. Customers can export limited information from your profile, such as name, headline, current company, current title, and general location, in order to manage sales leads or talent, unless you opt-out. We do not provide contact information to customers as part of these Pro Services without your consent. A Pro Services customer can store information he/she has about you in our Pro Services, such as a resume or contact information or sales history. The data provided about you by these customers is subject to the policies of those customers.

#### 2.3 Communications

We contact you and enable communications between Members. We offer settings to control what messages you receive and how often you receive some types of messages.

We will contact you through email, mobile phone, notices posted on our websites or apps, messages to your EITCA Academy inbox, and other ways through our Services, including text messages and push notifications. We will send you messages about the availability of our Services, security, or other service-related issues. We also send messages about how to use the Services, network updates, reminders, job suggestions and promotional messages from us and our partners. You may change your communication preferences at any time. Please be aware that you cannot opt-out of receiving service messages from us, including security and legal notices.

We also enable communications between you and others through our Services, including for example invitations, InMail, groups and messages between connections.

#### 2.4 Advertising

We serve you tailored ads both on and off our Services. We offer you choices regarding personalized ads, but you cannot opt-out of seeing other ads.

We target (and measure the performance of) ads to Members, Visitors and others both on and off our Services directly or through a variety of partners, using the following data, whether separately or combined:

Data from advertising technologies on and off our Services, like web beacons, pixels, ad tags, cookies, and device identifiers;  
Participant-provided information (e.g., profile, contact information, title and industry);  
Data from your use of our Services (e.g., search history, feed, content you read, who you follow or is following you, connections, groups participation, page visits, videos you watch, clicking on an ad, etc.), including as described in Section 1.3;  
Information from advertising partners and publishers; and  
Information inferred from data described above (e.g., using job titles from a profile to infer industry, seniority, and compensation bracket; using graduation dates to infer age or using first names or pronoun usage to infer gender).  
We will show you ads called sponsored content or advertisement which look similar to non-sponsored content, except that they are labeled “ads” or “sponsored.” If you take an action (such as like, comment or share) on these ads, your action is associated with your name and viewable by others, including the advertiser. Subject to your settings, if you take a social action on our Services, that action may be mentioned with related ads.

#### Ad Choices

We adhere to self-regulatory principles for interest-based advertising and participate in industry opt-outs from such ads. This does not opt you out of receiving advertising; you will continue to get other ads by advertisers not listed with these self regulatory tools.

#### Info to Ad Providers

We do not share your personal data with any third-party advertisers or ad networks for their advertising except for: (i) hashed or device identifiers (to the extent they are personal data in some countries); (ii) with your separate permission (e.g., lead generation form) or (iii) data already visible to any users of the Services (e.g. profile). However, if you view or click on an ad on or off our site or apps, the ad provider will get a signal that someone visited the page that displayed the ad, and they may through the use of mechanisms such as cookies determine it is you. Advertising partners can associate personal data collected by the advertiser directly from you with our cookies and similar technologies. In such instances, we seek to contractually require such advertising partners to obtain your explicit, opt-in consent before doing so.

#### 2.5 Marketing

We promote our Services to you and others.

We use data and content about Members for invitations and communications promoting membership and network growth, engagement and our Services.

#### 2.6 Developing Services and Research

We develop our Services and conduct research.

#### Service Development

We use data, including public feedback, to conduct research and development for the further development of our Services in order to provide you and others with a better, more intuitive and personalized experience, drive membership growth and engagement on our Services, and help connect professionals to each other and to economic opportunity.

#### Other Research

We seek to create economic opportunity for Members of the global workforce and to help them be more productive and successful. We use the personal data available to us to research social, economic and workplace trends such as jobs availability and skills needed for these jobs and policies that help bridge the gap in various industries and geographic areas. In some cases, we work with trusted third parties to perform this research, under controls that are designed to protect your privacy. We publish or allow others to publish economic insights, presented as aggregated data rather than personal data.

#### Surveys

Polls and surveys are conducted by us and others through our Services. You are not obligated to respond to polls or surveys, and you have choices about the information you provide. You may opt-out of survey invitations.

#### 2.7 Customer Support

We use data to help you and fix problems.

We use the data (which can include your communications) to investigate, respond to and resolve complaints and Service issues (e.g., bugs).

#### 2.8 Aggregate Insights

We use data to generate aggregate insights.

We use your data to produce and share aggregated insights that do not identify you. For example we may use your data to generate statistics about our members, their profession or industry, to calculate ad impressions served or clicked on, or to publish visitor demographics for a Service or demographic workforce insights.

#### 2.9 Security and Investigations

We use data for security, fraud prevention and investigations.

We use your data (including your communications) if we think it’s necessary for security purposes or to investigate possible fraud or other violations of our User Agreement or this Privacy Policy and/or attempts to harm our Members or Visitors.

#### 2.10 Identity Verification

The Participant’s identity has to be verified for the remote online certification procedure to be implemented. The identity verification is based on Participant’s input personal data and securely uploaded scan of an identity document (either a national ID document or a passport) processed only to complete the identity verification. This information is collected and processed only for the purpose of verifying the identity of certification programmes participants, and will be used only for that purpose.

We are committed to protecting the privacy of the European IT Certification programmes participants and their personal information. The security of certification programmes participants’ personal information is the top priority of EITCI, and it ha implemented strict security measures to protect it from any unauthorized access. Only authorized personnel implementing identifcation verification procedures will have access to this information. The personal information we collect to validate all implemented certification procedures will be stored during the period of participation in the corresponding certification programmes and during the period of certification validity accordingly with the Certification Agreement.

Participants’ personal data is processed in line with the provisions of the European General Data Protection Regulation, i.e. Regulation (EU) 2016/679 on the protection of individuals in view of processing of their personal private data, in order to enable online implementation of the European IT Certification process. Participants have the right to request access to, correction of, or deletion of your personal information at any time. To exercise these rights, please contact us as instructed in 5.5. Contact Information.

#### 3\. How We Share Information

#### 3.1 Our Services

Any data that you include on your profile and any content you post or social action (e.g. likes, follows, comments, shares) you take on our Services will be seen by others.

#### Profile

Your profile is fully visible to all Members and customers of our Services. Subject to your settings, it can also be visible to others on or off of our Services (e.g., Visitors to our Services or users of third-party search engines).

#### Posts, Likes, Follows, Comments, Messages

Our Services allow viewing and sharing information including through posts, likes, follows and comments.

When you share an article or a post (e.g., an update, image, video or article) publicly it can be viewed by everyone and re-shared anywhere (subject to your settings). Members, Visitors and others will be able to find and see your publicly-shared content, including your name (and photo if you have provided one).  
In a group, posts are visible to others in the group. Your membership in groups is public and part of your profile, but you can change visibility in your settings.  
Any information you share through companies’ or other organizations’ pages on our Services will be viewable by it and others who visit those pages.  
When you follow a person or organization, you are visible to others and that “page owner” as a follower.  
We let senders know when you act on their message, subject to your settings where applicable.  
Subject to your settings, we let a Participant know when you view their profile.  
When you like or re-share or comment on another’s content (including ads), others will be able to view these “social actions” and associate it with you (e.g., your name, profile and photo if you provided it).  
Your employer can see how you use Services they provided for your work (e.g. as a recruiter or sales agent) and related information. We will not show them your job searches or personal messages.

#### Enterprise Accounts

Your employer may offer you access to our enterprise Services. Your employer can review and manage your use of such enterprise Services.

Depending on the enterprise Service, before you use such Service, we will ask for permission to share relevant data from your profile or use of our non-enterprise Services.

#### 3.2 Communication Archival

Regulated Members may need to store communications outside of our Service.

Some Members (or their employers) need, for legal or professional compliance, to archive their communications and social media activity, and will use services of others to provide these archival services. We enable archiving of messages by those Members outside of our Services. For example, a financial advisor needs to archive communications with her clients through our Services in order to maintain her professional financial advisor license.

#### 3.3 Others’ Services

You may link your account with others’ services so that they can look up your contacts’ profiles, post your shares on such platforms, or start conversations with your connections on such platforms. Excerpts from your profile will also appear on the services of others.

Subject to your settings, other services may look-up your profile. When you opt to link your account with other services, personal data will become available to them. The sharing and use of that personal data will be described in, or linked to, a consent screen when you opt to link the accounts. For example, you may link your Twitter or WeChat account to share content from our Services into these other services, or your email provider may give you the option to upload your EITCA Academy contacts into its own service. You may revoke the link with such accounts.

Subject to your settings, excerpts from your profile will appear on the services of others (e.g., search engine results, mail and calendar applications that show a user information from EITCA Academy profile of the person they are meeting or messaging, social media aggregators, talent and lead managers). “Old” profile information remains on these services until they update their data cache with changes you made to your profile.

#### 3.4 Related Services

We share your data across our different Services and EITCA Academy affiliated entities.

We will share your personal data with our affiliates to provide and develop our Services. We may combine information internally across the different Services covered by this Privacy Policy to help our Services be more relevant and useful to you and others.

#### 3.5 Service Providers

We may use others to help us with our Services.

We use others to help us provide our Services (e.g., maintenance, analysis, audit, payments, fraud detection, marketing and development). They will have access to your information as reasonably necessary to perform these tasks on our behalf and are obligated not to disclose or use it for other purposes.

#### 3.6 Legal Disclosures

We may need to share your data when we believe it’s required by law or to help protect the rights and safety of you, us or others.

It is possible that we will need to disclose information about you when required by law, subpoena, or other legal process or if we have a good faith belief that disclosure is reasonably necessary to (1) investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual illegal activities or to assist government enforcement agencies; (2) enforce our agreements with you, (3) investigate and defend ourselves against any third-party claims or allegations, (4) protect the security or integrity of our Service (such as by sharing with companies facing similar threats); or (5) exercise or protect the rights and safety of EITCA Academy, our Members, personnel, or others. We attempt to notify Members about legal demands for their personal data when appropriate in our judgment, unless prohibited by law or court order or when the request is an emergency. We may dispute such demands when we believe, in our discretion, that the requests are overbroad, vague or lack proper authority, but we do not promise to challenge every demand.

#### 3.7 Change in Control or Sale

We may share your data when our business is sold to others, but it must continue to be used in accordance with this Privacy Policy.

We can also share your personal data as part of a sale, merger or change in control, or in preparation for any of these events. Any other entity which buys us or part of our business will have the right to continue to use your data, but only in the manner set out in this Privacy Policy unless you agree otherwise.

4\. Your Choices & Obligations
------------------------------

#### 4.1 Data Retention

We keep most of your personal data for as long as your account is open.

We retain your personal data while your account is in existence or as needed to provide you Services. This includes data you or others provided to us and data generated or inferred from your use of our Services. Even if you only use our Services when looking for a new job every few years, we will retain your information and keep your profile open until you decide to close your account by informing us about it (e.g. by email). In some cases we choose to retain certain information in a depersonalized or aggregated form.

#### 4.2 Rights to Access and Control Your Personal Data

You can access or delete your personal data. You have many choices about how your data is collected, used and shared.

We provide many choices about the collection, use and sharing of your data, from deleting or correcting data you include in your profile and controlling the visibility of your posts to advertising opt-outs and communication controls. We offer you settings to control and manage the personal data we have about you.

#### For personal data that we have about you:

Delete Data: You can ask us to erase or delete all or some of your personal data (e.g., if it is no longer necessary to provide Services to you).  
Change or Correct Data: You can edit some of your personal data through your account. You can also ask us to change, update or fix your data in certain cases, particularly if it’s inaccurate.  
Object to, or Limit or Restrict, Use of Data: You can ask us to stop using all or some of your personal data (e.g., if we have no legal right to keep using it) or to limit our use of it (e.g., if your personal data is inaccurate or unlawfully held).  
Right to Access and/or Take Your Data: You can ask us for a copy of your personal data and can ask for a copy of personal data you provided in machine readable form.  
You may also contact us using the contact information on our website, and we will consider your request in accordance with applicable laws.

Residents in the Designated Countries may have additional rights under their laws.

#### 4.3 Account Closure

We keep some of your data even after you close your account.

If you choose to close your EITCA Academy account, your personal data will generally stop being visible to others on our Services within 24 hours. We generally delete closed account information within 30 days of account closure, except as noted below.

We retain your personal data even after you have closed your account if reasonably necessary to comply with our legal obligations (including law enforcement requests), meet regulatory requirements, resolve disputes, maintain security, prevent fraud and abuse, enforce our User Agreement, or fulfill your request to “unsubscribe” from further messages from us. We will retain de-personalized information after your account has been closed.

Information you have shared with others will remain visible after you closed your account or deleted the information from your own profile or mailbox, and we do not control data that other Members copied out of our Services. Groups content and ratings or review content associated with closed accounts will show an unknown user as the source. Your profile may continue to be displayed in the services of others (e.g., search engine results) until they refresh their cache.

5\. Other Important Information
-------------------------------

#### 5.1. Security

We monitor for and try to prevent security breaches. Please use the security features available through our Services.

We implement security safeguards designed to protect your data, such as HTTPS. We regularly monitor our systems for possible vulnerabilities and attacks. However, we cannot warrant the security of any information that you send us. There is no guarantee that data may not be accessed, disclosed, altered, or destroyed by breach of any of our physical, technical, or managerial safeguards. Please visit our Safety Center for additional information about safely using our Services, including two-factor authentication.

#### 5.2. Cross-Border Data Transfers

We store and use your data outside your country.

We process data both inside and outside of the United States and rely on legally-provided mechanisms to lawfully transfer data across borders. Countries where we process data may have laws which are different, and potentially not as protective, as the laws of your own country.

#### 5.3 Lawful Bases for Processing

We have lawful bases to collect, use and share data about you. You have choices about our use of your data.

At any time, you can withdraw consent you have provided by going to settings and chaning the date you choose to provide and access to this data by others.

We will only collect and process personal data about you where we have lawful bases. Lawful bases include consent (where you have given consent), contract (where processing is necessary for the performance of a contract with you (e.g. to deliver the Services you have requested)) and “legitimate interests”.

Where we rely on your consent to process personal data, you have the right to withdraw or decline your consent at any time and where we rely on legitimate interests, you have the right to object. If you have any questions about the lawful bases upon which we collect and use your personal data, please contact us.

#### 5.4. Direct Marketing and Do Not Track Signals

Our statements regarding direct marketing and “do not track” signals.

We currently do not share personal data with third parties for their direct marketing purposes without your permission.

#### 5.5. Contact Information

You can contact us or use other options to resolve any complaints.

If you have questions or complaints regarding this Policy, please first contact EITCI Institute online visiting [https://eitca.org/contact](https://eitca.org/contact). You can also contact EITCI Institute with all contact details available on the website [https://eitci.org](https://eitci.org/).

### Regulations & Policies

### CERTIFICATES SEARCH

Search for:  

### CERTIFICATES ACCESS

* [EITC Certification](https://eitca.org/certification-category/eitc/) (105)
* [EITCA Certification](https://eitca.org/certification-category/eitca/) (9)

### PROGRAMME TAGS

### MOST RATED

*  [ EITC/BI/CAPMF Computer-aided project management fundamentals](https://eitca.org/certification/eitcbicapmf-computer-aided-project-management-fundamentals/) € 110.00
*  [ EITC/BI/SDBAMS Spreadsheets and databases in business applications (MSO Excel, MS Access)](https://eitca.org/certification/eitcbisdbams-spreadsheets-and-databases-in-business-applications-mso-excel-ms-access/) € 110.00
*  [ EITC/INT/JOOM Website design and content management systems fundamentals (Joomla)](https://eitca.org/certification/eitcintjoom-website-design-and-content-management-systems-fundamentals-joomla/) € 110.00
*  [ EITC/WD/WPF WordPress Fundamentals](https://eitca.org/certification/eitc-wd-wpf-wordpress-fundamentals/) € 110.00
*  [ EITC/BI/MSOPP Multimedia presentation software fundamentals (Microsoft Office)](https://eitca.org/certification/eitcbimsopp-multimedia-presentation-software-fundamentals-microsoft-office/) € 110.00
*  [ EITC/CG/AI1 Vector graphics processing software (Adobe Illustrator)](https://eitca.org/certification/eitccgai1-vector-graphics-processing-software-adobe-illustrator/) € 110.00
*  [ EITC/CG/ADPD Artistic digital portrait drawing](https://eitca.org/certification/eitc-cg-adpd-artistic-digital-portrait-drawing/) € 110.00

### What are you looking for?

### EITCA Academy is a part of the European IT Certification framework

The European IT Certification framework has been established in 2008 as a Europe based and vendor independent standard in widely accessible online certification of digital skills and competencies in many areas of professional digital specializations. The EITC framework is governed by the [European IT Certification Institute (EITCI)](https://eitci.org/), a non-profit certification authority supporting information society growth and bridging the digital skills gap in the EU.### Eligibility for EITCA Academy 80% EITCI DSJC Subsidy support

80% of EITCA Academy fees subsidized in enrolment by      

### EITCA Academy Administrative Office

Brussels, Belgium, European Union

The EITC / EITCA Certification Authority  
Governing European IT Certification Standard  
Access [contact form](https://eitca.org/contact) or call [+32 25887351](tel:+3225887351)

Funded by the [European Regional Development Fund (ERDF)](https://ec.europa.eu/regional_policy/funding/erdf_en) and the [European Social Fund (ESF)](https://european-social-fund-plus.ec.europa.eu/en), governed by the [EITCI Institute](https://eitci.org/european-it-certification-recognition) since 2008

* [](https://zh-cn.eitca.org/privacy-policy/ "Chinese (Simplified)")
* [](https://zh-tw.eitca.org/privacy-policy/ "Chinese (Traditional)")
* [](https://my.eitca.org/privacy-policy/ "Myanmar (Burmese)")

Select LanguageAfrikaansArabicBelarusianBengaliBosnianBulgarianCatalanChinese (Simplified)Chinese (Traditional)CroatianCzechDanishDutchEnglishEstonianFilipinoFinnishFrenchGeorgianGermanGreekHebrewHindiHungarianIndonesianItalianJapaneseJavaneseKoreanKurdishLatvianLithuanianMalayMongolianMyanmar (Burmese)NepaliNorwegianPashtoPersianPolishPortuguesePunjabiRomanianRussianSerbianSlovakSlovenianSpanishSwedishTamilTeluguThaiTurkishUkrainianUrduVietnamese

Automatically translate to your language

* EITCA Academy on social media

© 2008-2024  [European IT Certification Institute](http://eitci.org/)  
Brussels, Belgium, European Union

Chat with Support

Chat with Support

Questions, doubts, issues? We are here to help you!

[End chat](javascript:void(0))

Connecting...

Do you have any questions?

Do you have any questions?

Your name :

Your email address :

Your question :

[Send](javascript:void(0))

Do you have any questions?

Your name :

Your email address :

[Start Chat](javascript:void(0))

The chat session has ended. Thank you!

Please rate the support you've received.

[Good](javascript:void(0)) [Bad](javascript:void(0))

 Have a copy of the chat be sent to your e-mail for a future reference.
